Preliminary Guide to the Takey Crist Papers, 1944-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession, 2007 (2007-0043), 35 Boxes
  - Crist Clinic Subject Files Series
    - Meeting - 1992, Sept. 23-27, International Congress of Gynecologic Endoscopy, Chicago (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1993, May 1-6, ACOG Annual Clinical Meeting, Washington DC (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1993, Dec. 1-5, Postgraduate Course, NY (Box 19)
    - Menopause (Box 19)
    - Menstruation (Box 19)
    - Menstrual Extraction (Box 19)
    - Mental Health (Box 19)
    - Mental Retardation (Box 19)
    - Midwives (Box 19)
    - Migraine (Box 19)
    - Miscarriage (Box 19)
    - Modern Concepts of Cardiovascular Disease (Box 19)
    - Mononucleosis, Infectious (Box 19)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, undated (Box 19)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 19)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1984 (Box 19)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1987 (Box 20)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 20)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1988 (Box 20)
    - Moral Majority Clippings, 1989 (Box 20)
    - Morning After Pill (Box 20)
    - Morning-Sickness (Box 20)
    - Mortality Statistics (Box 20)
    - Mumford, Stephen (Box 20)
    - Myometrium (Box 20)
    - NARAL (Box 20)
    - NARAL-NC Newsletter (Box 20)
    - NARAL News (Box 20)
    - National Organization for Non-Parents (Box 20)
    - NAVCARE (Box 20)
    - North Carolina Child Advocacy Institute (Box 20)
    - North Carolina Civil Liberties Union (Box 20)
    - North Carolina Coalition for Choice, Minutes (Box 20)
    - North Carolina Medical Peer Review Foundation (Box 20)
    - North Carolina Student Legislature (Box 20)
    - Nursing Practice (Box 20)
    - Nurse Practitioner Program - ECU (Box 21)
    - Obesity (Box 21)
    - Ob-Gyn (Box 21)
    - OB-GYN Dept., NC Memorial Hospital (Box 21)
    - Ob-Gyn References (Box 21)
    - Obstetrics (Box 21)
    - Obstetrical Emergency - Patient Care (Box 21)
    - Office Management (Box 21)
    - Onslow County Medical Society (Box 21)
    - Onslow County School Board (Box 21)
    - Onslow Memorial Hospital (Box 21)
    - Operating Room Technician - Coastal Carolina CC (Box 21)
    - Ophthalmology (Box 21)
    - Oral Sex (Box 21)
    - Osteoporosis (Box 21)
    - Out-patient Surgery (Box 21)
    - Ovary (Box 21)
    - Ovulation (Box 22)
    - Oxytocin (Box 22)
    - Pain (Box 22)
    - Pain, Abdominal (Box 22)
    - Pap Smear (Box 22)
    - Parasites (Box 22)
    - Parental Notification (Box 22)
    - Parenthood (Box 22)
    - Parvovirus (Box 22)
    - Paternity Testing (Box 22)
    - Patient Education (Box 22)
    - Patient Information Booklets (Box 22)
    - Pediatrics (Box 22)
    - Pelvic Infections (Box 22)
    - Pelvic Inflammatory Disease (Box 22)
    - Pelvic Pain (Box 22)
    - Pelvimetry (Box 22)
    - Penis (Box 22)
    - People for the American Way, North Carolina (Box 23)
    - Perinatalogy (Box 23)
    - Peritoneal Adhesions (Box 23)
    - Pessary (Box 23)
    - Phenobarbital (Box 23)
    - Pheochromocytoma (Box 23)
    - Philosophy in Medicine (Box 23)
    - Phlebitis (Box 23)
    - Physician Assistants (Box 23)
    - Physicians for Choice (Box 23)
    - Impaired Physician (Box 23)
    - Physician Resources, Inc. (Box 23)
    - Physicians' Washington Report (Box 23)
    - Physicians, Women (Box 23)
    - Placebo Effect (Box 23)
    - Placenta (Box 23)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 23)
    - Planned Parenthood of Greater Charlotte (Box 23)
    - Planned Parenthood - World Population (Box 23)
    - Plastic Surgery (Box 23)
    - PMS (Box 23)
    - Pneumonia (Box 23)
    - Polio Vaccine (Box 23)
    - Polycystic Ovarian Disease (Box 23)
    - Polyps Endometrial (Box 23)
    - Population (Box 23)
    - Pornography (Box 23)
    - Postmenopausal (Box 23)
    - Postpartum hemorrhage (Box 23)
    - Pregnancy (Box 23)
    - Pregnancy Complications (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy - Dental Health (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy and Diabetes (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy -- Endocrine (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy - Heart Disease (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy - Hypertension (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy - Nutrition (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy - Postpartum Depression (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy - Postterm (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy Rate, unintended (Box 24)
    - Pregnancy Test (Box 24)
    - Pregnant Pause (Box 24)
    - Premarital Counseling (Box 24)
    - Premature Fetus (Box 24)
    - Premature Labor (Box 24)
    - Premenstrual Dysphoric Disorder (Box 24)
    - Prenatal Care (Box 24)
    - Prenatal Diagnosis (Box 24)
    - Prenatal HIV (Box 24)
    - Pro-Choice Resource Center (Box 24)
    - Professional Diet Service (Box 24)
    - Professional Research Inc. (Box 24)
    - Progesterone (Box 24)
    - Prostaglandin (Box 24)
    - Prostitution (Box 25)
    - Pruritus Vulvae (Box 25)
    - Pulmonary Disease (Box 25)
    - Pulmonary Embolism (Box 25)
    - Quinacrine Sterilization (Box 25)
    - Rape (Box 25)
    - Rape - Newspaper Clippings (Box 25)
    - Rectum (Box 25)
    - Religion (Box 25)
    - Religion - Catholics (Box 25)
    - Religion - Episcopal Church (Box 25)
    - Religion - Freedom from Religion Foundation (Box 25)
    - Religion -- Jehovah's Witnesses (Box 25)
    - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights (Box 25)
    - Reproductive Toxicology (Box 25)
    - Respiratory Infections (Box 25)
    - Reye's Syndrome (Box 25)
    - RH-disease (Box 25)
    - Rhinitis (Box 25)
    - Rhogam (Box 26)
    - Ritalin (Box 26)
    - Rubella Vaccine (Box 26)
    - Ruptured Membranes (Box 26)
    - Safe Sex (Box 26)
    - Sex Addiction (Box 26)
    - Sex and Disability (Box 26)
    - Sex Education, undated (Box 26)
    - Sex Education, 1968-1979 (Box 26)
    - Sex Education, 1980-1989 (Box 26)
    - Sex Education, 1990s (Box 26)
    - Sex Education Correspondence (Box 26)
    - Sex Education: Egg Project - Parrott Academy (Box 27)
    - Sex and the Elderly (Box 27)
    - Sex and the Physician (Box 27)
    - Sexual Abuse (Box 27)
    - Sexual Behavior (Box 27)
    - Sexual Counseling (Box 27)
    - Sexual Counseling, Interact Phone Interview (Box 27)
    - Sexual Dysfunction (Box 27)
    - Sexual Function (Box 27)
    - Sexual Law Reporter (Box 27)
    - Female Sexuality (Box 27)
    - Male Sexuality (Box 27)
    - Sexual Medicine Today (Box 27)
    - Sexually Transmitted Diseases, undated (Box 28)
    - Sexually Transmitted Diseases, 1970s (Box 28)
    - Sexually Transmitted Diseases, 1980s and 1990s (Box 28)
    - Sexually Transmitted Diseases Bulletin (Box 28)
    - STD - Chlamydia (Box 28)
    - STD -- Genital Warts (Box 28)
    - STD -- Gonorrhea (Box 28)
    - STD -- Herpes (Box 28)
    - STD -- Syphilis (Box 28)
    - Shock, Treatment of (Box 28)
    - Shoulder Dystocia (Box 28)
    - Siamese Twins (Box 28)
    - Sickle Cell Anemia (Box 29)
    - SIECUS (Box 29)
    - SIECUS 15th Anniversary Meeting, 29 Nov. 1979 (Box 29)
    - Sleep (Box 29)
    - Smallpox (Box 29)
    - Smoking (Box 29)
    - Speaker Tips and Hints (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, Feb. 20, Queens College (Box 29)
    - (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, Feb. 22 and March 1, UNC-C, Population Workshop (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, March 30-31, Edinboro Collge, PA (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, April 8-11, Marshall University, Sex Symposium (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, April 26-27, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, May 7-11, American Psychiatric Association, Hawaii (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, June 7-10, Maryland Academy of Family Physicians (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1973, Nov. 7 and 14, Sex Symposium, NCSU (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Jan. 31, Roanoke Valley League for Planned Parenthood (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Feb. 2, UNC-C, Population Workshop (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, March 11, Educational Seminar on Population Control, Kinston, N.C. (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, April 29-May 2, Annual Clinical Program ACOG, Venereal Disease Box 30 (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, May 17, NAACOG, Richmond (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Oct. 16-20, PPFA Annual Meeting, St. Louis (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Nov. 3, Trinity United Methodist Church, Jacksonville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Nov. 9, FHA Jacksonville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Nov. 13-14, NC Family Planning Advisory Council, Quail Roost, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1974, Nov. 26, Family Planning Workshop, New Bern (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, Feb. 7, Seminar on Human Sexuality, Univ. of South Dakota (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, Feb. 13, Population Workshop UNC-Charlotte (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, Feb. 16, Chapel Hill Jaycees (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, April 15, Family Life Education Committee, Onslow County Family Planning Council Seminar (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, May 4, St. Anne's Episcopal Church, Teenage Speech (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, May 12-13, Family Planning Seminar, UNC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, May 28, AHEC Human Sexuality Symposium, Jacksonville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, June 1-2, Human Sexuality in Medical Practice, audio cassettes (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, Oct. 8, Onslow Academy, Sex Education (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1975, Oct. 30, Staff NCO Club, Camp Lejeune, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1976, March 10, Pre-Marriage Course, Westminster College, PA (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1976, March 22, Meredith College, Sex Symposium (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1976, April 10, Nurses Association of the ACOG, Winston-Salem, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1976, April 30, Emergencies in Ob-Gyn, Goldsboro, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1976, May 23-27, International College of Surgeons, Athens, Greece (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1976, Oct. 14-15, Adolescent Pregnancy Prevention Management, Charlotte, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Jan. 12, Junior Women's League, Fayetteville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, March 11, Danville-Pittsylvania County Academy of Medicine (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, April 1, Lob-Holly Dental Society (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, May 6, Auxiliary to the North Carolina Medical Society, Pinehurst, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, May 12, ACOG Impact Symposium, Chicago (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, July 1-9, AASECT, Cabris, France (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Sept. 28, 5th District Medical Society, Pinehurst, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Oct. 11, EAHEC Maternal Health Conference, Greenville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Oct. 21-23, AASECT, 2nd Annual southeastern Regional Conference, Asheville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Oct. 29, Mental Health Fair, Smithfield, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Nov. 3, Statewide Family Planning Project Administrators' Conference, Gulf Shores, AL (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Nov. 8, TV-Program MacNeil/Lehrer Report "Abortion" (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Nov. 13-15, Dept. of HEW Conference on Teenage Pregnancy, Atlanta (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Nov. 15, Medical Auxiliary, Wilmington NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1977, Dec. 9-11, Community Sex Information Inc., New York (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, March 5, AASECT National Conference, Teenagers and Contraception (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, April 5-6, Human Sexuality Symposium, Westminster College, PA (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, April 19, Medical Meeting, Hickory, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, May 18-19, Workshop on Pregnancy and Adolescent Development, South Carolina Dept. of Health (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, May 19-21, NC Nurses Association of the ACOG, Wilmington, NC Box 31 (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, June 2, AHEC/NC Nurses Association, Adolescent Health Workshop (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, June 16, Graduating Class James Sprunt Institute (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, June 19-20, PPFA Teenage Conference, Charlotte, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, June 21, Onslow County Department of Social Services (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, June 29-30, South Central Region Teen Workshop, Southern Pines, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, July 5, Abortion Debate with Dr. Nolan, Chicago (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, Aug. 10, Abortion Program WCTI-TV (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, Sept. 5, AMA Medical Assistants and Nurses, Kinston Hospital (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, Sept. 5, Continuing Education Program, Cleveland Memorial Hospital, Shelby, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, Sept. 27, Fayetteville Area Public Nurses Association (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, Oct. 21-25, NC Ob-Gyn Society, Kiawah, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1978, Dec. 4-6, Dept. of HEW, Workshop on Teenage Pregnancy, Irving, TX (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, Jan. 8, American Association of Medical Assistants Lecture (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, Jan. 17, Teenage Pregnancy, Wake County Medical Society (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, Jan. 25, Abortion Debate, Channel 11, Durham NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, April 9-11, Adolescent Sexuality Workshop, Birmingham AL (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, April 17, Columbia County Medical Society [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, April 27, Family Planning Lecture, Greensboro, NC [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, May 30, Nurse Practitioners, Abortion, ECU [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, June 14-16, Seaboard Medical Society, Virginia Beach, VA [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, June 29, Teenage Pregnancy and Abortion, Manteo, NC [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, Aug. 9, Annual Summer Conference Home Economics Teachers, Winston Salem, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1979, Dec. 1, Lenoir County Mental Health Association (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Feb. 19, North Carolina Personnel and Guidance Association, Winston Salem, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Feb. 22, Medical Update, Miami, FL [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, March 8, FHA NC Association, Raleigh NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, April 2, Continuing Education Lecture, Orlando FL [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, April 16, Westminster College, PA (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, May 6, NAACOG, Virginia Section, Norfolk VA [Searle & Co] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, May 14, Freedom High School, Morganton, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Aug. 25, ECU School of Nursing (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Sept. 17, Update in Obstetrics and Gynecology, Canton OH -- cancelled (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Oct. 6, Sex Education Week, Shelby NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Oct. 21, John Rock Commemorative Meeting, Philadelphia PA (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Oct. 28, Onslow Human Services Council (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Nov. 8, SC Family Practice Meeting, Charleston, SC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Nov. 16, Woman Adolescent Sexuality, Raleigh NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1980, Dec. 4, Sexuality is More than Sex, Russell Sage College, Albany NY [Searle & Co.] (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1981, Jan.-June, Division of Health Services, Family Planning Branch Training, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1981, Jan. 27, Workshop on Prevention and Treatment of Child Abuse and Neglect, Jacksonville, NC (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1981, April 3, Kentucky OB/GYN Society (Box 29)
    - Speech - 1981, April 21, School of Public Health, UNC-Chapel Hill (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1981, Oct. 11, NAACOG District IV, Charlotte, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1982, May 1, North Carolina OBGYN Society, Southern Pines, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1982, May 27, NC Social Services Association, Raleigh, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1982, June 3, Rural Health Care in the 80s, Charleston, SC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1982, Oct. 22, NC Social Services Association Meeting, Brunswick Co., NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1982, Oct. 26, NC Social Services Association, Annual conference, Wrightsville Beach, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1982, Dec. 1, NCSU, Human Sexuality (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1983, March 24, Salem College, Winston Salem, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1983, April 22, Gaston County Dept. of Social Services, Gastonia, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1983, May 5, North Carolina Medical Society, Public Health & Education, Pinehurst, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1983, June 22, Onslow Memorial Hospital, Emergency Nurse Education Program (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1983, Sept. 26, Child Abuse, Southeast Regional Education Center, Jacksonville, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1984, April 18, Abortion Counseling, NC Dept. of Social Services (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1985, May 9, Eastern District Public Health Association, Wilmington, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1986, Jan. 16, Burke Citizens for CHOICE, Morganton, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1986, March 5, Wake Teen Medical Services, Raleigh, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1986, April 23, Physicians' Assistants Refresher Course, Fayetteville, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1986, May 7, Abortion In-service, Nurses, Onslow Memorial Hospital (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1987, Jan. 24, North Carolina Coalition for Choice, Raleigh, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1987, March 11, Dixon High School, Holly Ridge, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1987, April 9, Duke Society of Medical Legal Affairs, Durham, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1987, Sept. 25, Ob-Gyn Residents, ECU School of Medicine (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1989, April 26, Raleigh, NC, NARAL Speak-Out (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1990, April 28, Abortion Rally, Raleigh, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1991, Jan. 22, Roe Vs. Wade Commemoration (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1992, Jan. 29, Pembroke State Univ., Pembroke, NC (Box 32)
    - Speech - 1993, Jan. 21, Planned Parenthood Charlotte, NC (Box 32)
    - Speeches (Box 32)
    - Speeches, Correspondence 1973 (Box 32)
    - Speeches, Correspondence 1974 (Box 32)
    - Speeches, Correspondence 1980s (Box 32)
    - Sperm Bank (Box 32)
    - Splenomegaly (Box 32)
    - Sterilization, undated, 1959-1979 (Box 32)
    - Sterilization 1980-present (Box 32)
    - Steroids (Box 33)
    - Streptococcal (Box 33)
    - Stroke (Box 33)
    - Student Papers (Box 33)
    - Students Rights (Box 33)
    - Sudden Infant Death Syndrome (Box 33)
    - Suicide (Box 33)
    - Summer Field Placement Fellowship, 1975 (Box 33)
    - Surgery - Pregnancy (Box 33)
    - Surgery Techniques (Box 33)
    - Surrogate Mothers (Box 33)
    - Swine Flu (Box 33)
    - Syndicated Ad Features (Box 33)
    - Teenagers (Box 33)
    - Teenage Patient (Box 33)
    - Teenage Pregnancy, undated (Box 33)
    - Teenage Pregnancy, 1960s (Box 33)
    - Teenage Pregnancy, 1970s (Box 34)
    - Teenage Pregnancy, 1980s and 1990s (Box 34)
    - Teenage Pregnancy: Carteret Community Action Report (Box 34)
    - Teenage Pregnancy Programs (Box 34)
    - Teenage Sexuality (Box 34)
    - Testosterone (Box 34)
    - Tetanus (Box 34)
    - Thermography (Box 34)
    - Thrombocytopenia (Box 34)
    - Thromboembolic Disease (Box 34)
    - Thrombosis (Box 34)
    - Thyroid (Box 34)
    - Tinnitus (Box 34)
    - Toxemia of Pregnancy (Box 34)
    - Toxic Shock (Box 34)
    - Toxic Shock Patient Questionnaire (Box 35)
    - Transsexuals (Box 35)
    - Tuboplasty (Box 35)
    - Twin Pregnancy (Box 35)
    - Ulcer (Box 35)
    - Ultrasound (Box 35)
    - UNC Medical Students, Class of 1965 (Box 35)
    - Urinary Incontinence (Box 35)
    - Urinary Tract Infections (Box 35)
    - Uterine Bleeding (Box 35)
    - Uterine Rupture (Box 35)
    - Uterus (Box 35)
    - Vagina (Box 35)
    - Vaginal Birth After Cesarean (Box 35)
    - Vaginitis (Box 35)
    - Valium (Box 35)
    - Vascular Birthmarks (Box 35)
    - Vasectomy (Box 35)
    - Viagra (Box 35)
    - Violence (Box 35)
    - Virginity (Box 35)
    - Vitamin C (Box 35)
    - Vitamin E (Box 35)
    - Von Willebrand Disease (Box 35)
    - Woman's Healthletter (Box 35)
    - Women's Liberation (Box 35)
    - X-rays and pregnancy (Box 35)
    - Zero Population Growth (Box 35)